question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
     "question": "In the &quot;Shrek&quot; film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The band STRFKR was also briefly known as Pyramiddd.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "General Knowledge",
     "question": "&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Animals", "question": "Rabbits can&#039;t vomit.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "During Wimbledon, spectators in the grounds can buy the tennis balls that have been used in matches.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga",
     "question": "In the &quot;To Love-Ru&quot; series, Peke is considered a female robot.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "&quot;Windows NT&quot; is a monolithic kernel.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Sean Connery wasn&#039;t in &quot;Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull&quot; because he found retirement too enjoyable.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In RuneScape, one must complete the &quot;Dragon Slayer&quot; quest before equipping Rune Platelegs.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Mythology",
     "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Mythology", "question": "A wyvern is the same as a dragon.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Sports",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Geography",
     "question": "Liechtenstein does not have an airport.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Science: Computers",
     "question": "The common software-programming acronym &quot;I18N&quot; comes from the term &quot;Interlocalization&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "History",
     "question": "The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
